A Guide to the Fairfax County Public Library System Map Collection, 1894-1977
Library of Virginia
- Accession 5892L, Blacksburg Engineering Department, "Town of Blacksburg, Virginia", 30 x 23 inches, Scale ca. 1:14,600,1973. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892M, United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service South Region, "Appalachian Trail Map 4, Glenwood, Newcaste Ranger Districts, Jefferson National Forest", 19 x 28.5 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1993. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892N, United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service Southern Region, "Appalachian Trail Map Three, Blacksburg Ranger District, Jefferson National Forest", 28.5 x 18.75 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1993. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892O, [City of Richmond] Metro Chamber of Commerce, "Metro Richmond Street Map with Classified Business Locator Index", 39 x 25 inches, Scale 1:52,000,1980. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892P, Rand McNally, "Rand McNally Richmond Street Map", 31.5 x 17 inches, Scale 1 in. = approx. 0.62 miles,1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892Q, Colonial Williamsburg, "Map of Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia", 19 x 23.75 inches, Scale 1:3,000,ca.1960-1968. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892R, "Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia, Richmond City Zip Codes", 8.5 x 11 inches,1979. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892S, Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce, City of Richmond", 11 x 17 inches, Scale 1:32,000,1976. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892T, Waynesboro-East Augusta Chamber of Commerce, "Street Map of the City of Waynesboro, Virginia", 19 x 25 inches, Scale 1:22,000,1981. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892U, "Street Map of the City of Waynesboro, Virginia", 18.75 x 25 inches, Scale ca. 1:22,000,1977. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892V, Staunton-Augusta County Chamber of Commerce, "Staunton, Virginia", 19 x 25 inches, Scale in feet,1982. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892W, Richmond City Planning Commission, "The Richmond Tour", 7.25 x 8 inches, Scale not given,No date. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892X, Richmond Metropolitan Authority, "A Guide to Richmond's Expressway System, Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce, City of Richmond", 17.5 x 19.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1976. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5892Y, Rand McNally and Co., "Richmond Street Map", 32 x 17 inches, Scale 1:39,283,1978. (Folder 5)
- Accession 5896, Gary Cauble, "Champion Map of Bristol, Virginia-Tennessee Including a Detailed Map of Sullivan and Washington Counties", 20 x 26 inches, Scale 1:24,000 and 1:180,000,1977. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896A, United States Forest Service Southern Region, "Jefferson National Forest, Wythe and Holston Ranger Districts, North Section/South Section", 16 x 40.25 inches, Scale in miles,1960s. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896B, Hugo Stevens, "A Map Showing the Points of Interest in Jamestown, Williamsburg and Yorktown in Virginia", 12.75 x 18 inches, Scale in miles,1930. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896C, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Smith Mountain Lake", 20.5 x 33 inches, Scale 1:24,000 and 1:2,000, (W 79°52’--W 79°31’/N 37°14’--N 36°59’),1981. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896D, Alexandria Drafting Company, "Lake Gaston", 20.5 x 33, 1:24,000 and 1:2,000, Polyconic projection, (W 78°16’--W 77°48’/N 36°38’--N 36°28’),1981. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896E, Petersburg Chamber of Commerce, "Official Map City of Petersburg, Virginia Together with Facts and Information about the City and Its Environs, January 1, 1972", 12.75 x 16.25 inches, Scale not given,1977. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896F, Portsmouth Chamber of Commerce, "Portsmouth Virginia City Map", 17.5 x 14.75 inches, Scale 1:29,000,No date. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896G, Harrisonburg Electric Commission, "Map of Harrisonburg, Virginia and Environs, Revised Dec. 1974", 15.5 x 21 inches, Scale 1:16,000,1974. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896H, Rand McNally and Company, "Norfolk and Hampton Roads Area, Including Chesapeake, Hampton, Newport News, Portsmouth", 24 x 16.5 inches, Scale 1:42,451,1978. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896I, Rodney Mayhew, "Champion Map of Roanoke, Virginia Including Salem and Vinton", 21 x 19.5 inches,No date. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896J, Metropolitan Richmond Chamber of Commerce, "City of Richmond", 15 x 10.25 inches, Scale 1:32,000,1976. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896K, Champion Map Corporation, "The Great Metro Richmond See and Do Map", 38.75 x 24.75 inches, Scale 1:52,500,1980. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896L, Portsmouth Chamber of Commerce, "Portsmouth Virginia City Map", 17.5 x 14.75 inches, Scale 1:29,000,No date. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896M, Jim and Rachel Graves, "Graves Mountain Lodge in the Blue Ridge Mountains", 8 x 12.75 inches, Scale not given,No date. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896N, Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Highways and Transportation, "Interstate-Arterial Highway System of Virginia", 9.5 x 17.25 inches, Scale of miles,1976. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896O, Champion Map Corporation, "Map of Charlottesville, Albemarle County, Virginia", 36 x 24 inches, Scale 1:18,500,1979. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896P, Greater Lynchburg Chamber of Commerce, "Street Map of Lynchburg and Environs", 28.25 x 21.25, Scale in feet,1978. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896Q, Christiansburg Chamber of Commerce, "Christiansburg Virginia Town Map", 16 x 16.5 inches, Scale not given,1975. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896R, [Fairfax County Division of Mapping], "Metrobus Service Route Map for Fairfax County", 25.75 x 26 inches, Scale 1:50,000,1979. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896S, K.L. Wyatt, "Our Portsmouth Heritage National Register of Historic Places City of Portsmouth, Virginia", 19.5 x 11.5 inches, Scale given,1978. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896T, U.S. Constitution Sesquicentennial Commission, "Massachusetts (Eastern Part, i.e. the District of Maine) at the Time of the Ratification of the Constitution, from Original Map in the Library of Congress at Washington, Including One Based upon a Mitchell Map Owned and Used by John Jay", 17 x 17 inches, Scales vary,1938. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896U, Champion Map Corporation, "Champion Road Map of Virginia", 16.75 x 34.75 inches, Scale 1:800,000,1988. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5896V, Rand McNally and Co., "United States Map Featuring Civil War Battlefields and Sites", 36 x 26 inches, Scale 1:7,300,000 and Scale 1:3,900,000,1961. (Folder 6)
- Accession 5900, John D. Marr, "Geology of the Andersonville Quadrangle, Virginia", 28.75 x 41.75 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1980. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900A, Van Price, "Geology of the Whitmell and Brosville Quadrangles, Virginia", 47.5 x 35.75 inches, Scale 1:24,000, (W 79°37’30”--W 79°30’00”/N 36°45’00”--N 36°32’30”),1980. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900B, Van Price, "Geology of the Axton and Northeast Eden Quadrangles, Virginia", 47.5 x 35.75 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1980. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900C, John Donald Marr, "Geology of the Willis Mountain Quadrangle, Virginia", 28.75 x 41.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000, (W 78°30’--W 78°22’30”/N 37°30’--N 37°22’30”),1980. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900D, R.E. Weems, "Geology of the Hanover Academy Quadrangle, Virginia", 28.75 x 41.5 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1981. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900F, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax", 1 map on 4 sheets, scales vary,1977. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900G, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Prepared by Fairfax County Planning Division", 42.5 x 38.5 inches, Scale given,1964. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900H, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Prepared by Fairfax County Planning Division", 42 x 37 inches, scale given,1962. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900I, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County Virginia Prepared by Fairfax County Planning Division", 42.25 x 37 inches, Scale given,1963. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900J, U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, "United States East Coast Virginia Chesapeake Bay Entrance",14th edition, 32 x 42 inches, Scale 1:80,000,1953. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900K, U.S. Geological Survey, "Topographic Map Shenandoah National Park Virginia, South Half", 34.75 x 33.75 inches, Scale 1:62,500,1955. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900L, Stanley S. Johnson, "Bouguer Gravity and Total Intensity Magnetic Map, Albemarle County", 42 x 35 inches, Scale 1:62,500,(W 78°50’--W 78°12’/N 38°17’--N 37°43’),1969. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900M, James F. Conley, "Structure of the Philpott Reservoir Quadrangle, Virginia", 22.5 x 18 inches, Scale 1:24,000,1969. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900N, Arlington County Department of Community Affairs Planning Division, "General Land Use Plan Arlington County, Virginia, Adopted August 12, 1961, with Amendments through March 24, 1979", 40 x 26 inches, Scale 1:14,400,1969. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900O, U.S. Geological Survey and National Park Service, "1:25,000 Scale Topographic Map of Colonial National Historical Park", 23.75 x 44.75 inches, Scale 1:25,000,(W 76°15’50”--W 76°29’00”/N 37°19’00”--N 37°10’45”),1981. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900P, Prince William County Planning Office, "Magisterial Districts and Voting Precincts, Prince William County, Virginia", 33 x 31 inches, Scale 1:63,360,1983. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900Q, Northern Virginia Regional Planning and Economic Development Commission, "Northern Virginia Regional Plan Year 2000", 42 x 58 inches, Scale 1:130,000,(W 77°10’19”--W 77°01’55”/N 38°56’03”--N 38°49’38”),1965. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900R, U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, "United States East Coast, Maryland and Virginia Chesapeake Bay, Southern Region", 29.25 x 31 inches, Scale not given,1930. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900S, U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, "United States East Coast, Maryland and Virginia Potomac River, Piney Point to Lower Cedar Point", 10th edition, 32.5 x 43.75 inches, Scale 1:40,000 ,1969. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900T, Commonwealth of Virginia, "Virginia Aeronautical Chart, 1981-1982", 26 x 58.25 inches, Scale in nautical and statute miles,1981. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900U, United States Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census Geography Division, "Boundaries of Counties and County Equivalents as of January 1, 1970", 25 x 37.75 inches, Scale 1:5,000,000; Albers equal area projection,1970. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900V, United States Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, "Boundaries of Counties and County Equivalents as of January 1, 1970", 25 x 37.75 inches, Scale 1:5,000,000; Albars equal area projection,1971. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900W, Donald A. Wise, "Map of Colonial Patents, Grants and Treasury Warrants in Arlington County, Virginia", 47.75 x 35.75 inches, Scale 1:5,700,1975. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900X, Arlington County Department of Community Affairs Planning Division, "General Land Use Plan, Arlington County, Virginia, Adopted August 12, 1961, with Amendments through March 24, 1979", 40 x 26 inches, Scale 1:14,000,1979. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900Y, Commonwealth of Virginia, "Virginia Aeronautical Chart, 1984-1985", 27 x 58 inches, Scale 1:500,000,1984. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5900Z, United States Bureau of the Census, "West Virginia Subdivisions Magisterial Districts and Places", 29.5 x 34 inches, Scale 1:500,000, (W 82°39’--W 77°44’/N 40°38’--N 37°12'),1971. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5901, Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, "Maryland County Subdivisions, Election Districts and Places; Delaware County Subdivisions, Census County Divisions and Places", 16.75 x 29.5 inches and 13 x 6.25 inches, Scales given,1971. (Folder 8)
- Accession 5901A, Fairfax County Division of Mapping, "Commonwealth of Virginia County of Fairfax, Fairfax County Industrial Authority", 42 x 36.5 inches,1970. (Folder 8)
- Accession 5901B, Fairfax County Communications Division, "County of Fairfax, Commonwealth of Virginia, Sub Census Tracts, 1985-1986", 42 x 36.75 inches, Scale in feet and miles,1984. (Folder 8)
- Accession 5901C, Fairfax County Development Authority, "Commonwealth of Virginia, County of Fairfax Office and Industrial Zoning", 42 x 36.5 inches, Scale in feet,1977. (Folder 7)
- Accession 5901D, Fairfax County Planning Division, "Fairfax County, Virginia, Prepared by Fairfax County Planning Division", 42.25 x 37 inches, Scale given,1963. (Folder 8)